Ralph E. Flanders Papers
Ralph E. Flanders Papers
- General correspondence files
  - General correspondence, 1934-1937
    - New York Museum of Science & Industry (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - New York Times (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - New York University (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Nolen, John (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Norfleet, Helen (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Norman, Carl A. (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - North Dakota State Engineer (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Northwestern University (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Norwich University & Board of Trustees (Box 38, Folder 1-3)
    - Noxon, Frank W. (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Noyes Buick Sales Company (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - N, General (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Ohio State University (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Old Colony Railroad Company (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Old First Church of Bennington (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Old Rockingham Meeting House Association (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - O'Leary, John W. (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Oliphant, A. C. (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - O'Mahoney, Sen. Joseph C. (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Orcutt, John C. (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Ordway, Bernice P. (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Orrok, George A. (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Otterbein, George C. (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - O, General (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Paine, Wilfred A. (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Painter, Levinus K. (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Pan American Airways (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Paramount Manufacturing Company (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Park, Franklin A. (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Parker, John (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Parlini, A. C. (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - Partridge, Frank C. (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - Patterson, Ernest Minor (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - Pearson, Eleanor C. (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - Peek, George N. (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - Pennsylvania State College (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Pepperell, W. S. (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Perkins, Miss Frances (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Perkins, Lynn F. (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Perkins, Thomas N. (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Person, Harlow S. (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Persons, Warren M. (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Peters, Arthur C. (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Peterson, Nathaniel C. (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Pettengill, Samuel B. (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Pfleiderer, Emil (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Pierson, Lewis E. (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Pegman, Augustus (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Pinchot, Amos (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Pitt, Courtney (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Plumley, Charles A. (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Pope, Russel H. (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Porter, Russell W. (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Porter, A. A. (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Pratt, Frederick B. (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Presbery Leland Studios (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Preston, Jerome (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Princeton Club of New York (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Princeton University (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Public Affairs Committee (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - Purcell, Charles H. (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - Purdue University (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - P, General (Box 39, Folder 29)
    - Railway Age (Box 39, Folder 30)
    - Raskob, John J. (Box 39, Folder 31)
    - Raymond, Fairfield E. (Box 39, Folder 32)
    - Raymond, H. E. (Box 39, Folder 33)
    - Reed College (Box 39, Folder 34)
    - Review of Reviews (Box 39, Folder 35)
    - Richie, Robert Y. (Box 39, Folder 36)
    - Robinson, Ernest L. (Box 39, Folder 37)
    - Roe, Joseph W. (Box 39, Folder 38)
    - Rollins College (Box 39, Folder 39)
    - Roper, Daniel C. (Box 39, Folder 40)
    - Rose, Edwin L. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Rose Polytechnic Institute (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Royal Economic Society (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Rutland Herald (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Rust, David D. (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Rutgers University (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - R, General (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Sackett, R. L. (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Sails, Carroll Morgan (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Saperston, Sidney (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Sargent, James B. (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Saturday Review of Literature (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Scamilion, Rolland J. (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Science Advisory Board (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Science Press, The (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Scott, Frank A. (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Scoville, J. W. (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Scribner's Magazine (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Sea Pines School (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Segur, A. B. (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Sellers, Coleman (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Sellers, M. K. (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Sharpe, Charles E. (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Sherburne, H. K. (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - Shewhart, Walter (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - Shoudy, W. A. (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - Shrader, William (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - Siman, S. G. (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - Simon, L. A. (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - Simonds, Alvan, T. (Box 40, Folder 30)
    - Simonds, Arthur P. (Box 40, Folder 31)
    - Slichter, Sumner (Box 40, Folder 32)
    - Sloan, George A. (Box 40, Folder 33)
    - Sloan, Larence H. (Box 40, Folder 34)
    - Sloan, Stella B. (Box 40, Folder 35)
    - Sloanaker, R. M. (Box 40, Folder 36)
    - Smiley, P. K. (Box 40, Folder 37)
    - Smith, Charles M. (Box 40, Folder 38)
    - Smith, C. E. (Box 40, Folder 39)
    - Smith, J. Spencer (Box 40, Folder 40)
    - Smith, James (Box 40, Folder 41)
    - Smith, Ralph (Box 40, Folder 42)
    - Snyder, Carl (Box 40, Folder 43)
    - Social Science Research Council (Box 40, Folder 44)
    - Social Security Board (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Social For Advancement of Management (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Society of the Genesee (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Society for Stability in Money & Banking (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Socony Vacuum Oil Company (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Sound Money League (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Southern Pacific Lines (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Spargo, John (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Spaulding, Archibald (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Speak-O-Phone Recording & Equipment Company (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Speare, Charles L. (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Springfield Muncipal Manager's Office (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Springfield Reporter (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Springfield Young Republican Club (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Standard Oil Company (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Standard Oil Company of New York (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Standard Statistics Company (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Stanford University (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Stannard, E. T. (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - State Forester (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Stevens Institute (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - St. Lawrence, John (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Stoddard, Alexander J. (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Strawn, Silas (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Summer Institute for Social Progress At Wellesley (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Sumner, William Graham (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - The Sun (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Superintendent of Documents, office of (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - Swasey, Ambrose (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Swift, Mrs. Charles N. (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - S, General (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - Taplin, F. C. Company (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - Tax Policy League (Box 41, Folder 33)
    - Taylor, Gladys (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Taylor, Alonzo E. (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Taylor, Henry E. (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Taylor Society (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Teagle, Walter C. (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Terry, Duncan Niles (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Texas Christian University (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Texas, University of (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Third World Power Conference (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Thomas, Arthur H. (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Thompson, Sanford E. (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Thompson, William R. (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Thorp, Willard L. (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Thorp, Gilbert H. (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Thrift & Security Foundation (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Tougaloo College (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Towson, Charles R. (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Tribit, Charles H. (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Triest, Rudolph (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Tucker, Gilbert M. (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Tucker, Rufus S. (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Turgeon, Newton E. (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - Turnbull, William (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - Tuttle, Charles F. Company (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - Unemployment Compensation Act (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - Unemployment Insurance (Box 42, Folder 27)
    - Unemployment Relief (Box 42, Folder 28)
    - Union Pacific Railroad Company (Box 42, Folder 29)
    - Union of the Soviet Socialistic Republic Chamber of Commerce (Box 42, Folder 30)
    - United Church of Ludlow, Vermont (Box 42, Folder 31)
    - United States Constitution Sesquicentennial Commission (Box 42, Folder 32)
    - United States Department of Agriculture (Box 42, Folder 33)
    - United States Department of Commerce (Box 42, Folder 34)
    - United States Department of Interior (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - United States Employment Service (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - United States Forestry Survey (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - United States Treasury Department (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - United States Weekly (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - United States Works Progress Administration (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Upson, Walter L. (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - U, General (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Valentine, A. L. (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Vancouver Sun (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Vandiest, Edmond C. (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Vauclain, Samuel M. (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Verein Deutscher Ingenieure (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Vermont, University of (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Vermont Agricultural Experiment Station (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Vermont Association for Billboard Restriction (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Vermont, Auditor of Accounts, See Gates, Benjamin
    - Vermont Children's Aid Society (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Vermont Committee for the Fight Against Paralysis (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Vermont Conference of Social Work (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Vermont Congregational Conference (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - Vermont Guild of Old Time Crafts and Industries, Form Letter (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - Vermont Guild of Old Time Crafts and Industries (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - Vermont Horse and Bridle Trail Bulletin (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - Vermont League of Women Voters (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - Vermont Marble Company (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - Vermont Newspapers (Box 43, Folder 27)
    - Vermont Parkway (Box 43, Folder 28)
    - Vermont Publicity Service (Box 43, Folder 29)
    - Vermont Railroad Survey (Box 43, Folder 30)
    - Vermont Society of Buffalo (Box 43, Folder 31)
    - Vermont Society of Engineers (Box 43, Folder 32)
    - Vermont State Chamber of Commerce (Box 43, Folder 33)
    - Vermont State Farm Bureau (Box 43, Folder 34)
    - Vermont State Legislature (Box 43, Folder 35)
    - Viets, Paul W. (Box 43, Folder 36)
    - Vital Speeches (Box 43, Folder 37)
    - Von Hann, Baron (Box 43, Folder 38)
    - Voorhees, S. F. (Box 43, Folder 39)
    - V, General (Box 43, Folder 40)
    - Walbridge Realty Company (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Waldron, Frederick (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Walker, R. J. (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Wallace, Mrs. Fannie (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Wallace, Lawrence Wilkerson (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Wallen, James (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Warren Publications Incorporated (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Washington, University of (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Washington Navy Yard (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Watson, Thomas J. (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Watt Bicentenary (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Weber, Richard & Company (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Webster, S. T. (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Weil, Charles (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Weiss, Philip (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Wellington, Oliver (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Wentworth, R. A. (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Wernette, Philip (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Westerfield, Ray (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Weston Electric Instrument Corporation (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Westtown School (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - Who's Who Among Association Executives (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - Who's Who in Chicago (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - [John] Wiley and Sons, Inc. (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - Will, Folsom and Smith, Incorporated (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - Williams, Oliver (Box 44, Folder 26)
    - Williams, S. Clay (Box 44, Folder 27)
    - Williston, Arthur (Box 44, Folder 28)
    - Willits, Joseph H. (Box 44, Folder 29)
    - Willkie, Wendell L. (Box 44, Folder 30)
    - Wilmarth, Warren L. (Box 44, Folder 31)
    - Wilson, M. L. (Box 44, Folder 32)
    - Wilt, A. D., Jr. (Box 44, Folder 33)
    - Winant, John G. (Box 44, Folder 34)
    - Winterbotham, Joseph, See Champlain Valley Council
    - Winterrowd, W. H. (Box 44, Folder 36)
    - Winzenburger, Ernest A. (Box 44, Folder 37)
    - Wisconsin, University of (Box 44, Folder 38)
    - Wise, Roy T. (Box 44, Folder 39)
    - Witherow, William P. (Box 44, Folder 40)
    - Witte, Edwin E. (Box 44, Folder 41)
    - Wood, Arthur W. (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Wood, Katherine D. (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Wood, R. E. (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Woods, Ralph L. (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Woodward, Charles (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Woolridge, W. R. (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Worchester Boys' Trade School (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Works Progress Administration (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - World Economic & Monetary Conference (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - World Power Conference (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Wright, Roy V. (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Wyer, Samuel S. (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - York Chamber of Commerce (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Young, Mason J. (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Young, Ralph A. (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Young Republicans (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Young Men's Christian Association of Glens Falls, New York (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Young Men's Christian Association of Vermont (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Yu, Tsune-Chi (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Y, General (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - Zimmerman, Oliver B. (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - Zur Nedden, F. (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - General correspondence, 1938-1939
    - Ackerman, P. (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Adams, F. B. (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Affleck, Benjamin F. (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Aiken, George D. (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Alford, L. P. (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - American Academy of Arts & Sciences (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - American Arbitration Association (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - American Engineering Council (Box 46, Folder 8-9)
    - American Express Company (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - American Legion (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - American Management Association (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - American Road Builders' Association (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - American-Russian Chamber of Commerce (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - American Society of Mechanical Engineers
      - Davies, C. F. (Box 47, Folder 2)
      - Hartford, Earnest (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - LePage, C. B. (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - Screw Thread Committee, Miscellaneous (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - Stetson, George (Box 47, Folder 6)
      - Sub-Committee on Screw Threads (Box 47, Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 47, Folder 8-9)
    - American Society of Planning Officials (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - American Society of Tool Engineers (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - American Standards Association (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - American Synergics (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - American Taxpayers League (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - American Tool Works (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - American Youth Movement (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Andersen Laboratories (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Animal Husbandry Department (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Antioch College (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Army Ordnance Association (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Associated Industries of Vermont (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Atlantic Monthly (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Austin, Warren R. (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Automobiles, Information on (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Automobile Club of Vermont (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - A, General (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Babitt, E. J. (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Babson Institute (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Bach Choir (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Bacon, Gaspar G. (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Baker, Charles Whiting (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Bauer, P. W. (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Barker, Harry (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Barnard, Chester I. (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Barradas League (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Barrett, William J. (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Batt, William L. (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Beal, Henry S. (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Beardslee, Ray (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Belisle, Eugene (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Blackmer, Samuel H. (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Blanchard, Herbert H. (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Bliss, Elmer J. (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Boca Raton Club (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Boston Automobile Club (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Bowman Orchard Company (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - Boy Scouts of America (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Brattleboro Trust Company (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Brehmer, William (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Brentano's (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Brigham, Elbert S. (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - British Consulate General (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Brown, Horace (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Brown, Ralph W. (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Brown, W. T. (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Brown & Sharpe Manufacturing Company (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Budd, Edward G. Manufacturing Company (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Buker, Henry (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Burlington Daily News (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Burlington Free Press (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Burr & Burton Seminary (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Burroughs, Robert P. (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Burt, Clayton (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Business Advisory Council (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Buttrick, David Company (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Buy American Institute (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - Byrnes, James F. (Box 50, Folder 21)
    - B, General (Box 50, Folder 22)
    - Canadian Pacific Railroad (Box 50, Folder 23)
    - Capital, Definition of (Box 50, Folder 24)
    - Carnegie Corporation (Box 50, Folder 25)
    - Carter, Henry (Box 50, Folder 26)
    - Casey, Leo J. (Box 50, Folder 27)
    - Castle, N. H. (Box 50, Folder 28)
    - Catholic Charities Incorporated (Box 50, Folder 29)
    - Central Hanover Bank & Trust Company (Box 50, Folder 30)
    - Central Vermont Railroad (Box 50, Folder 31)
    - Central Electric Company (Box 50, Folder 32)
    - Chamber of Commerce of United States (Box 50, Folder 33)
    - Champlain Valley Council (Box 50, Folder 34)
    - Chase, Charles H. (Box 50, Folder 35)
    - Chicago American (Box 50, Folder 36)
    - Chisnall, Richard (Box 50, Folder 37)
    - Christmas Cards Received (Box 50, Folder 38)
    - Chrysler Motors (Box 50, Folder 39)
    - Chung, T. C. (Box 50, Folder 40)
    - Church, M. D. (Box 50, Folder 41)
    - Cincinnati, Bickford Company (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Cincinnati Milling Machine Company (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Claremont Advocate (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Clark, Myron H. (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Clayton, Will L. (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Clement, Charles S. (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Clevenger, Clifford L. (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Coker, David R. (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Columbia University (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Commercial Club of Boston (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Committee for the Nation (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Committee on Cultural Relations with Latin America (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Commonwealth Federation of New York (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Community House (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Congregational & Christian Churches (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Congregational Church, Barton, Vermont (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Congregational Church, Brattleboro, Vermont (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Congregational Church, Jamaica Plain, Massachusetts (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Congregational Church, Littleton, New Hampshire (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Congregational Church, Newport, Vermont (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - Congregational Church, Springfield, Vermont (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Congregational Church, Wells River, Vermont (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - Congregational Society, First Unitarian, Burlington, Vermont (Box 51, Folder 23)
    - Connecticut Economic Council (Box 51, Folder 24)
    - Consumers Guild of America (Box 51, Folder 25)
    - Cooke, Harte (Box 51, Folder 26)
    - Coonley, Howard (Box 51, Folder 27)
    - Coonley, Prentiss L. (Box 51, Folder 28)
    - Cornell University (Box 51, Folder 29)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, Incorporated (Box 51, Folder 30)
    - Counihan, E. A. III (Box 51, Folder 31)
    - Courant, R. (Box 51, Folder 32)
    - Coward Show Store (Box 51, Folder 33)
    - Cowles Press, Incorporated (Box 51, Folder 34)
    - Creed of Management (Box 51, Folder 35)
    - Creed, Merrill E. (Box 51, Folder 36)
    - Creighton, Albert M. (Box 51, Folder 37)
    - Cressingham, Harold (Box 51, Folder 38)
    - Crooker, C. W. (Box 51, Folder 39)
    - Crowley, Jack (Box 51, Folder 40)
    - Cushman, Mrs. Robert (Box 51, Folder 41)
    - C, General (Box 51, Folder 42)
    - Dartmouth College (Box 51, Folder 43)
    - Davenport, Walter R. (Box 51, Folder 44)
    - Davenport, William S. (Box 51, Folder 45)
    - Davis, George S. (Box 51, Folder 46)
    - Davis, Harold M. (Box 51, Folder 47)
    - Dennison, Henry S. (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Deutsch, Z. G. (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Dexter, Roscoe M. (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Dienner, John Astor (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Diller, George E. (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Dimock, Julian A. (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Disaster Loan Corporation (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Ditt, Dawson (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Dooley, C. R. (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Dresden, Anton (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Dun & Bradstreet (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Dunn, Gano (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Dyer, John Napieer (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - D, General (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Eagle Press (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Early American Industries Association (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Econometric Society (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Economic Policy Committee (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Economists' National Committee (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Edie, Lionel (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - Engineers Club (Box 52, Folder 21)
    - Engineers Council for Professional Development (Box 52, Folder 22)
    - Fairchild, Sherman M. (Box 52, Folder 23)
    - Federal Council of Churches of Christ in America (Box 52, Folder 24)
    - Federal Reserve System, Board of Governors (Box 52, Folder 25)
    - Federated Church in Winchester (Box 52, Folder 26)
    - Fellows, Edwin R. (Box 52, Folder 27)
    - Fellows Gear Shaper Company (Box 52, Folder 28)
    - Ferris, John P. (Box 52, Folder 29)
    - Field, Crosby (Box 52, Folder 30)
    - Ford, Robert H. (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Foreign Policy Association (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Fortune (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Forum (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Foster, William T. (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Frank, Glenn (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - French, E. S. (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - (John) Fritz Medal Board of Award (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Gage Sub-Committee (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Galusha, Mrs. F. W. (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Gay, Leon S. (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - General American Life Insurance Company (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Gibson, Ernest W., Jr. (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Gilbreth, Mrs. Lillian M. (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Gilfillan, Claude (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Goddard College, Plainfield, Vermont (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Goddard Junior College, Barre, Vermont (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Gleason, Jim (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Gold, Bela (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Golden Gate Exposition (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Gordon, B. (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Graydon, Thomas H. (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Grenfell, Sir Wilfred (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Guild of Former Pipe Organ Pumpers (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - G, General (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Hamilton, Rolland J. (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Hammond, Robert (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Hancock, A. H. (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Hansen, Alvin (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Hard, Mr. & Mrs. Walter (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Hard, William (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Harper's Bazaar (Box 54, Folder 14)